<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Project 5 - My City Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Name of the welcome screen tab -->
    <string name="category_about">About</string>

    <!-- Name of the Fun tab -->
    <string name="category_fun">Fun</string>

    <!-- Name of the Food tab -->
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>

    <!-- Name of the Hotels tab -->
    <string name="category_hotels">Hotels</string>


    <string name="title_text">Name of the place</string>
    <string name="details_text">Description of the place</string>
    <string name="address_text">Address of the place</string>

    <!-- Description of the welcome page -->
    <string name="city_name">Brasov</string>
    <string name="city_description">City Highlights
        \n\nFringed by the peaks of the Southern Carpathian Mountains and resplendent with gothic,
        baroque and renaissance architecture, as well as a wealth of historical attractions, Brasov
        is one of the most visited places in Romania.

        \n\nFounded by the Teutonic Knights in 1211 on an ancient Dacian site and settled by the Saxons
        as one of the seven walled citadels, Brasov exudes a distinct medieval ambiance and has
        been used as backdrop in many recent period films.

        \n\nThe location of the city at the intersection of trade routes linking the Ottoman Empire and
        western Europe, together with certain tax exemptions, allowed Saxon merchants to obtain
        considerable wealth and exert a strong political influence in the region. This was reflected
        in the city\'s German name, Kronstadt, as well as in its Latin name, Corona, meaning Crown
        City (hence, the coat of arms of the city which is a crown with oak roots). Fortifications
        were erected around the city and continually expanded, with several towers maintained by
        different craft guilds, according to medieval custom.

        \n\nBrasov is home to one of the narrowest streets in Europe. The Rope Street (Strada Sforii)
        is approximately four feet wide and it links Cerbului Street with Poarta Schei Street. This
        street was initially used as an access route by firefighters.

        \n\nStroll around the old Town Hall Square (Piata Sfatului) where you can admire colorfully
        painted and ornately trimmed baroque structures. Take a peek inside the Black Church
        (Biserica Neagra), the largest gothic church in Romania. Its name derives from damage caused
        by the Great Fire of 1689, when flames and smoke blackened its walls. The interior is
        impressive and well-kept and houses one of the largest organs in Eastern Europe.
        Nearby are towering mountains, rolling fields, thick forests and villages with fortified
        churches.</string>
    <string name="fast_facts">Fast Facts \n\nLocation: Central Romania (Brasov County) \nSize: 28.5
        sq. miles (74 sq. km) \nElevation: 2,133 ft. (650 meters) \nPopulation: 275,000 \nInhabited
        since: 100 BC \nFirst documented: 1234 AD (Corona)</string>

    <!-- Fun category items -->
    <string name="fun_name_1">The Council Square and The Old Town Hall</string>
    <string name="fun_info_1">The Saxons built massive stone walls and seven bastions around the
        city that are still visible today, as well as ornate churches, elaborately trimmed buildings
        and one of the finest central squares in the country, said to be the spot to which the
        legendary Pied Piper led the children of Hamlin. Located at the heart of old medieval Brasov
        and lined with beautiful red-roofed merchant houses, the Council Square, known to the Saxon
        population as the Marktplatz, is a nice place to rest and soak in the beautiful scenery.
        \n\nThe Old Town Hall was built in the 13th century, the house served as meeting place for
        the town councilors, known as centurions. On top of the building sits the Trumpeter\'s Tower,
        used during the Middle Ages as a watchtower for warning the citadel inhabitants of
        approaching danger. Today, the old city hall houses the Brasov History Museum.</string>
    <string name="fun_address_1">Address: Piata Sfatului 30</string>

    <string name="fun_name_2">The Black Church</string>
    <string name="fun_info_2">Built between 1385 and 1477 on the site of an earlier church
        (destroyed by Mongol invasions in 1242), the construction of the Marienkirche, as it was
        known in German, was hampered by extensive damage caused by Turkish raids in 1421. The
        church was given its new name after disaster struck again in 1689, when the Great Fire
        leveled most of the town, blackening the walls of the church. Restoration took almost 100
        years. Of two towers planned, only one was finished.
        \nThe original gothic interior got a makeover during restorations, and the lofty, light
        space you see today is mostly baroque. The interior is beautiful, with balconies, stained
        glass windows, an enormous organ, stone columns and walls adorned with fabulous Turkish
        carpets. The church windows have recently been fitted out with special UV-filtering glass
        to protect the 119 Anatolian carpets. Thankful to have survived their trips into the
        "barbaric" lands south and east of the Carpathians, German merchants donated the carpets to
        the church in the 17th and 18th centuries. The collection is the largest of its kind in
        Europe.
        \nListen to the impressive 4,000-pipe organ dating from 1839 during concerts held here
        three times a week in the summer.
        \n\nOpen:
        \nMon - Sat 10:00 am - 3:30 pm (September 16 – June 14);
        \nMon - Sat 10:00 am - 5:00 pm (June 15 – September 15);
        \nClosed Sunday
        \n\nOrgan concerts are held during the summer:
        \nJune and September: Tuesday (6:00 pm)
        \nJuly and August: Tuesday, Thursday, Saturday (6:00 pm)
        \nAdmission charge</string>
    <string name="fun_address_2">Address: Johannes Honterus Court 2</string>

    <string name="fun_name_3">The Art Museum</string>
    <string name="fun_info_3">The ground and first floors of the museum feature a national gallery
        of canvases, starting with anonymous Transylvanian painters of the 18th century up to the
        who\'s who of Romanian 20th century artists, including Theodor Pallady, Nicolae Grigorescu,
        Stefan Luchian and Horia Bernea.
        \nThe museum also displays works by Brasov-born Janos Mattis-Teutsch (1884-1960), one of the
        most influential Romanian artists, as well as sculptures by Corneliu Medrea, Ion Jalea,
        Frederic Storck and Dimitrie Paciurea.
        \n\nFrench photographer Brassai, famous for his portrayal of Paris at the beginning of the
        20th century, was born in 1899 in Brasov. Upon his move to France he took on his artistic
        pseudonym Brassai, which means \'from Brasov\'.
        \nVisit the cellar level for a look at the beautiful European crystal and porcelain, as well
        as a large collection of Oriental vases and statuettes from China, Tibet and Persia.
        \n\nAdmission charge.</string>
    <string name="fun_address_3">Address: Eroilor Bld. 21 A \nTel: 0268 477 286 \nWeb: www.muzeulartabv.ro
        \nOpen: \nTuesday - Sunday: 10:00 am - 6:00 pm \nClosed Monday</string>

    <string name="fun_name_4">Poiana Brasov</string>
    <string name="fun_info_4">A 15-minute drive or 30-minute bus ride from Brasov leads to Poiana
        Brasov (3,300 feet), a mountaintop ski and summer resort. During winter months, Poiana
        Brasov offers some of the best skiing in Romania. In the summer, it is a great place for
        hikers to launch treks into the Southern Carpathian Mountains. For a panoramic view of
        Brasov and the more distant Bucegi Mountains, take the cable car to the summit of Postavarul
        Mountain (5,756 feet).</string>
    <string name="fun_address_4">Where: 5 miles SW of Brasov \nAccess: Bus #20 leaves every half-hour
        from Livada Postei bus station</string>

    <!-- Food category items -->
    <string name="food_name_1">La Ceaun </string>
    <string name="food_info_1">Small traditional restaurant serving mainly soups and stews, cooked
        fresh every day with local ingredients.
        \n\nOpen Hours \nSunday: 12:00 PM - 10:00 PM \nMonday: 12:00 PM - 10:00 PM \nTuesday: 12:00
        PM - 10:00 PM \nWednesday: 12:00 PM - 10:00 PM \nThursday: 12:00 PM - 10:00 PM \nFriday:
        12:00 PM - 10:00 PM \nSaturday: 12:00 PM - 10:00 PM</string>
    <string name="food_address_1">Address 1: Weiss Michael Street Nr. 27 \nPhone Number: +40 773 936
        766 \n\nAddress 2: Piata Sfatului 11-12 \nPhone Number: +40 773 727 990</string>

    <string name="food_name_2">Casa Tudor </string>
    <string name="food_info_2">Pork greaves with red onions and fresh bread, on the house! The cooks
        are prepared to pamper your taste buds. The menu features a large variety of fresh products
        obtained from Sergiana’s own farms, as well as number of international dishes.
        \n\nEspecially for those with world-class appetites, the Cook Book is open for lunch and
        dinner with generous snacks, tasty salads, delicious soups and fragrances, all kinds of
        Angus dishes and spectacular barbecues! The menu also includes fish dishes, from bold
        Mediterranean recipes with octopus and shrimp to local dishes with anchovies and carp brine.
        \n\nRegardless of your choice, you will discover that ALL’S FINE AND TASTY!
        \n\nYou’re welcome \nMonday – Sunday: 11:00 - 24:00</string>
    <string name="food_address_2">Address: Avram Iancu Street 58
        \nE-mail: restaurantcasatudor@sergiana.ro
        \nPhone:  0728 830 340 | 0268 428 070</string>

    <string name="food_name_3">Ceasu\' Rau</string>
    <string name="food_info_3">If a National Barbecue Championship were ever held, then the finals
        would always take place at Ceasu\’ Rău. This is what our regulars like to say about our
        restaurant, which is famous all around the town for its “mititei”, its beer and its traditional
        Romanian atmosphere. \nA kitchen that works around the clock and a recipe book just like
        grandma used to keep. Welcoming salons and a seasonless garden. Any visit at Ceasu\’ Rău
        starts with fresh bread and the restaurant’s renowned menu - no hour of the week must be
        wasted on an empty plate, just like wooden platters and red towels must always accompany
        your lunch.
        \n\nHot Romanian soup, finger-licking good chicken paprikas with dumplings, bean stew with
        smoked pork hocks, delicious mutton pastrami with polenta, the famous sausages from Poiana
        Mărului, hot-smoked grilled pork ribs - everything tastes even better than it sounds. Pamper
        your taste buds with all this Romanian food, that tastes home made and comes in large
        servings. \n\nYou’re welcome \nMonday – Sunday: 11:00 - 24:00</string>
    <string name="food_address_3">Address: Iuliu Maniu Street 56
        \nE-mail: restaurantceasurau@sergiana.ro \nPhone: 0723 297 993 | 0268 476 670</string>

    <string name="food_name_4">Pub &amp; Bistro NEC\'s</string>
    <string name="food_info_4">Italian cuisine is both healthy and tasty, as everyone knows -
        especially when it features the unmistakable flavor of the Sergiana products. After a walk
        around the town, take a break in the city center and pay us a visit. Serving methods? All
        of them: take-in, take-out and delivery.
        \nThe meat and the meat products from Sergiana Poiana Mărului - the best possible ingredients
        for any type of pizza! At Nec’s, you can enjoy your favourite pizza in the surprising Pizza
        Party version: with plenty of ingredients and supreme sizes.
        \n\nFor a truly unique experience, we also included bistro dishes, each one tastier than the
        others: tempting snacks, light sandwiches, pasta with spices from the gardens of Italy, or
        vegetarian salads. In order for your date to be even better, don’t forget that wine best suits
        a copious meal, and that lemonades are best served with ice.
        \n\nEnjoy! \n\nYou’re welcome \nMonday – Sunday: 10:00 - 24:00</string>
    <string name="food_address_4">Address: Iuliu Maniu Street 43 \nE-mail: necs@sergiana.ro
        \nPhone: 0728 024 202 | 0268 543 658</string>

    <!-- Hotels category items -->
    <string name="hotels_name_1">Aro Palace</string>
    <string name="hotels_info_1">With a history of over 70 years, being inaugurated with great fast
        in 1939, it is the only 5 star hotel in Brasov. \nIn 1963 it was expanded by building a new
        building, and in 2005 it was raised to 5-star standards. The hotel occupies a privileged
        position in the historic center of the city. \nThanks to the experience we have gained over
        the years, we have been able to harmonize business with pleasure in a very exceptional way,
        combining business with relaxation and offering the guarantee of services that meet your
        needs. \nThe hotel offers a total of 195 rooms, of which 188 double or single rooms, 3
        suites, 3 studios, 1 presidential apartment, 6 restaurants, 4 conference rooms, 1 spa, all
        of which are equipped with impeccable quality.</string>
    <string name="hotels_address_1">Address: Eroilor Bld., no. 27 \n\nReservations:
        \nTel: +40 268 478 800 \nTel: +40 268 476 699 \nFax: +40 268 478 889 \nFax: +40 268 475 228
        \n\nE-mail: \nbooking@aro-palace.ro \nhotelaro@aro-palace.ro</string>

    <string name="hotels_name_2">Chambers\'n Charm</string>
    <string name="hotels_info_2">A stylish villa located on the road to Poiana Brasov with an
        absolutely amazing sight to Tampa and Brasov just 3 km from the historic center. \nChambers\'n
        Charm a wonderful and luxurious with 9 spacious rooms, each decorated in a different theme,
        5 stars rated, created for those who appreciate the ambiance and outstanding service boutique
        hotels. \nCustomers from Chambers'n Charm typically seek more than comfort. When planning
        their stay, search for hotels that are significantly different appearance and atmosphere of
        the hotel chains and will be pleasantly surprised by what I find your destination.
        Our hotel has all rooms equipped with minibar, safe, plasma TV, free wireless internet,
        hairdryer, telephone.</string>
    <string name="hotels_address_2">Address: 27 Stejerisului Street \nGPS: 45.644397, 25.572029
        \nPhone: 0368 412 904 \nMobile:0733 016 512 \nEmail: chambers.charm@gmail.com
    </string>

    <string name="hotels_name_3">Capitol Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotels_info_3">Capitol Hotel is located in the center of Brasov, next to the Town
        Hall and the Central Park. Whether you are here for business or pleasure, it is the ideal
        place for clients who combine relaxation with work. The Capitol Hotel offers you 183 double
        rooms, a restaurant where you can choose culinary choices from international and traditional
        cuisine, with a maximum of 200 seats, and for those who want to relax, just a few steps away,
        awaits the Aro-Palace Wellness &amp; Spa Center for Recreation and Sports.</string>
    <string name="hotels_address_3">Address: Eroilor Bld. 19 \n\nReservations:
        \nTel: +40 268 418 920 \nFax: +40 268 472 999
        \n\nE-mail: hotelcapitol@aro-palace.ro</string>

    <string name="hotels_name_4">Coroana Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotels_info_4">Hotel Coroana is one of the architectural jewels of Brasov, being
        the oldest hotel in the city, the meeting place of great personalities of the time. Placed
        on the city\’s famous pedestrian street, close to the old town gate, close to the Council
        Square and the Black Church, the hotel attracts all gazes through the Art Noveau and Baroque
        architecture, being a historic monument.
        \nArchitects Schuller and Goldsmidt were inspired by the Munchen architecture, suggesting a
        symbolic building that pleased both aesthetically and functionally. The hotel\’s threshold
        was passed by important names of Romanian spirituality such as: George Cosbuc, Cincinat
        Pavelescu, Lucian Blaga, Emil Cioran, Octavian Goga. Here was also the first literary
        gathering in Brasov in 1923.
        \nThe original name was Krone Hotel, named after the old town (Kronstadt or Crown City),
        keeping the mystery of the legend and the myth underlying the name “Brasov”. </string>
    <string name="hotels_address_4">Address: Republicii Street 62 \n\nReservations:
        \nTel: +40 268 477 448 \nFax: +40 268 418 469
        \n\nE-mail: hotelcoroana@aro-palace.ro</string>

</resources>
